hello my name is garina welcome back to
another episode of hermitcraft and
you're probably wondering why there is
so much ugly glowstone around me 10
green points to those of you that can
guess
i am making my second infinity meeting
room for sahara so i did talk about this
last episode but i've actually started
making it and
boy oh boy does this take a lot of
resources i completely forgot since
building the last one just how long it
is i've spent hours and hours gathering
the necessary materials i went for the
slightly more grindy block of glowstone
this time instead of sea lanterns
but oh my goodness even hours in the
nether gathering all this glowstone is
nothing compared to all of the bits you
need
for everything else so for those of you
that don't know what an infinity room is
let's go and have a quick look in my
base here i've got this little room
and this is the infinity room now i've
actually put loads of quartz here we've
got some seats but normally it would be
just like this and you can't tell what's
up down side side everything now the way
you do this is you have a light source
and then you have an item frame
and then you have a map on the top
that's completely white now this is
quite an expensive thing so even though
this room looks like it's really big
it's actually not and it's only a few
blocks high so i'm scaling this project
up for a bigger meeting room that's
probably more confusing
how have i lost a map how is this even
possible maps just vanished huh
well either way i've been preparing
getting loads of compasses
loads of everything else but there's
still a few things that i've got to do
so as you can see i've got a lot of
compasses made this still won't be
enough i've got some empty maps which i
can craft up but one thing that we're
lacking is item frames a lot of it
because all of the leather is sold out
that's about as much leather as i could
find so i've got to make some more
and making more means breeding cows
that's basically it so i thought what we
would do is we'll get this like
glowstone box made and you can see this
is about twice the size of my current
infinity room i am slightly worried
about how much this room is going to lag
because every single map
is an entity and entities
mean lag and lo and behold i don't have
enough glowstone anyway
so i'm gonna have to do another grind
session in the nether so let's go and
grab as much leather as possible and
start the big grind so right at the
start of the hermitcraft season six
i made a little cow farm and they've
been in here ever since these are the og
cows so i'm basically gonna nab two of
these and bring them over to my main
base because i don't think i'm gonna
breed them here let's get another one
come on come on
yes right you guys stay there
you two
you are betsy and bertie i kind of feel
bad because i know what's going to
happen to these guys
ultimately none of them are going to
make it oh man i don't feel so good
about this there must be a better way to
get leather
in you go
and
we have two
so now all we got to do is block off all
the places where they might get into a
spot of bother
so no going into the nether no falling
down this hole so i've already prepared
a bit of wheat so let's get started and
here goes the first one
this is going to be a slow start and
then it's going to explode so this
should be really fun to watch
[Music]
ah
about three hours later no way maybe
four hours later
there's a lot of cows here a lot of cows
i've actually had to turn the sound off
now this is lagging the server a lot so
we're gonna have to get rid of these
there's no no doubt about it like these
cannot stay according to my f3
statistics there's well over a thousand
entities here 1 000 cows
this is incredible and betsy and bertie
are somewhere
in here and i actually want to make sure
that they make it out of here
um but it may
oh i don't know how to find them oh
betsy no no it's bertie bertie i'll come
back for you we'll find betsy we'll get
a lead and we'll get them both out of
here
now i know you're here somewhere
it just didn't feel right i named them
and everything i took them from their
home oh betsy
okay there's one let's let's rescue you
let's get you out of here all right
birdie i'm coming for you come on bertie
the originals are saved
but now i need the leather so
it's time to get to work on saying
goodbye to these guys
it's like it's the server's so laggy
it's in like slow motion
oh dear
i don't like that i don't like this i
think i'm just gonna skip to the end of
this
mission accomplished
but at what cost
at what cost i did not enjoy that i did
not enjoy that at all i think that's
probably one of the the worst things
i've ever had to do in this game but
look at all this leather that is
probably more leather than we're ever
going to need for the rest of the season
so thankfully i will never have to do
that again most likely but that is
definitely enough now remember one of
these is one item frame so this still is
all of this will probably get used maybe
except for a bit so
oh man
there's just one left
there's just one left we no we gotta
keep him we gotta keep this one
should hang my head in shame
whoa
it is it is just minecraft after all
remember it had to be done we had to get
the leather i would have bought it if i
could have but i couldn't well now that
that insanity is taken care of
uh i think it's time we actually cracked
on with the actual infinity room
i've now got this entire space made out
of glowstone which obviously took a long
time to do as well i'm not sure why i've
done this it's just been one long grind
but anyway what we can do is we can get
started on crafting up all of these item
frames because 64 of them isn't going to
go very far at all in fact let's see how
many that actually does admittedly more
than i thought but still one stack is
not gonna cut it i'm gonna need a lot
more of these
whoa
oh my goodness did you
did you see how fast that came oh my
goodness
that went down so fast
oh my
i don't even know why these guys spawned
in its day
right well seeing as this is going to
take a little while you know what i'm
just going to skip forward to when this
is done
guys
i really hate to admit this but i think
i've messed up quite badly so i've spent
this entire episode
trying to make this room but as you can
see
as i suspected
it gets really laggy and choppy
just as you look at it so if you take a
look at this you see you see up here
there's c and then there's e now e is
the entities that's the entities that
there are so there's one looking in this
direction two who knows what they are if
you turn around
there's over a thousand entities and
that is causing a lot of lag that
doesn't mean that we can't have an
infinity room
but it certainly means
we need to make this smaller i started
getting um pretty pretty far into the
creation of this
and
it's got a logged in and he went oh
what's going on
so i think we're gonna have to downsize
this meaning most of today's episode was
completely pointless so i'm definitely
going to have to sell all of this
leftover leather and all of those item
frames in my cart because
i barely need 25 of it all right let's
get this done i can't believe i've
wasted so much time today it's
unbelievable
i cannot believe how much time i've
spent on it
especially as it's about 25
of of the original size but as you can
see no lag whatsoever maybe a slight
twinge but barely noticeable but if you
go inside
the effect is exactly the same at the
end of the day but it is that little bit
smaller the infinity room has been
remade and repurposed for sahara but
because it is that little bit smaller i
thought what i'd do is i'd play a little
trick on our good buddies mumbo and
iskall for when i show them how this
works and in order to get out of here
that's that's the biggest issue with
this
there's no way out i don't even know if
i'm looking up or down ah i was looking
i was looking down
well let me show you what i'm going to
do here so obviously the plan is to have
a meeting up here and this is going to
have all of the parrot display and
everything and i've made some holes here
so the idea is i have a button that i
can press when we're having a meeting
standing here and we fall through we
fall through like this into the infinity
room and there's going to be holes there
and there for mumbo and iskaw but what i
thought would be really funny is i'm not
going to move around but i bet you the
iska and mumbo are going to move around
so i reckon what i'm gonna do is i'm
gonna put like a little pit in here
so that they fall down just like in the
g team base basically but they won't be
seeing it they're just gonna they're
gonna fall fall through on their own
maybe i could even let them in one by
one and then i'm gonna hide it using the
trapdoor trick you open all of these up
and then you put the item frames over
the top and they're gonna fall in what i
put down here
i'm not entirely sure yet but i think it
could be a lot of fun
obviously i'm gonna make sure that they
don't like fall in lava or something
maybe i put slime blocks eve like all
the way down to the bottom of bedrock
right with a slime block so that they
bounce
and then another infinity room and they
just have no idea where they are that
could be really confusing
but because these item frames will be
all the way at bedrock they shouldn't
load in and cause any lag to us
so let's test this out shall we we're
standing here having our meeting i press
the button and we all fall into the
infinity room i'm gonna stand still
because i know it's there but these guys
are going to move around and be like
whoa look oh oh no oh no oh look i fell
and they're going to be so confused they
could be really really funny obviously
this is just a temporary thing just for
a bit of a laugh they will not expect it
oh man how do i get out of here how do i
get out of here without going back into
the hole
i've trapped myself
there we go oh okay we're out the
infinity room is a rather dangerous
place in the end look how many resources
i have left over because of this all of
this item frames all of this all of this
glowstone all of the leather all of the
quartz it's been a massive grind for
resources but i didn't get to use any of
it well fortunately we are going to be
selling products so that's probably
going to be helpful but i did have an
idea for what we could do with this so
as you guys know i'm in charge of the
marketing for sahara hence why we've got
this boardroom marketing campaigns
and i wanted to test to see if something
would work since i've got all of these
leftover uh sugarcanes i'm going to
create some paper and what we're going
to do is a leaflet campaign or we're
going to try out we're going to try out
one just one person obviously sahara
isn't even open yet shop at sahara
doesn't mean anything because you can't
shop at sahara yet but if we go in with
this leaflet campaign on every single
hermit
i think it could be really funny but i
need to test it out first to see if this
works so i've got to spend a little bit
of time actually creating the leaflets
which means
a lot of typing hashtag shop
at sir hara
and now we've got to do this over and
over so i spent a little bit of time and
i've created 16 unique ones and it has
mainly hashtags shop at sahara but some
of them say shop at sahara some of them
say purchases for sand and then it
started getting a bit weird it's quite
difficult to do
27 versions of these like papers
something to do with sarah i'm not going
to show you all of these because whoever
we end up doing this flyer campaign on
it's going to be really interesting to
read all of the weird and wacky things
now all we've got to do because i'm the
only person online at the moment i've
just got to wait for someone to get
online we'll come back we'll
load these up and then i'll show you
exactly how we're going to deliver these
but while we wait let's continue with
our elytra course because i have done a
little bit of work to it the main thing
that i've done is change the rings to be
a material that blends in with their
surroundings so for example here it is
still a circle and i did say that
there's not a lot i can do about making
this actually fit in
because they've they've obviously got to
be checkpoints but they do fit in they
don't just stand out in like glowstone
or something ugly so they do match it
that is a spruce ring over there so it
fits in with the dirt around it so let
me show you the course so far i haven't
actually done much more than last time
but you go down through the first one
through here you got a hairpin turn you
go down here now i haven't actually
finished the rings here but you can see
and then i want you to turn and go
through a ring here and then through the
ice one and then it's a little bit open
for debate so i think what i'm gonna do
is make just a couple more rings
to make this actually fit in
and we'll take it from there but this is
basically how it's going to shape up
and i've decided that i need to actually
give some sort of indicator on where to
go so obviously there's going to be like
a a banner that says one two three four
five but i actually need to tell them
where they need to go so i think the
main thing is they need to have a look
at the map or the course beforehand
because this is kind of complicated it's
best that they just test it out first
without actually racing
oh
ren ren's here
i didn't even see him what's this
he's a
is rena hippie now
ren hey are you a hippie
what's
who's ren
um
[Music]
g i wonder i'm renbob man
man is he here i'm red bob man
all right ren
you do you
i'm just here for the logs
i didn't even notice him
he's
actually trying to get around with a
boat ren that's not gonna work
that's really not gonna work i think
yeah i think he's realized that as well
what on earth and there's a hippie van
here
there's a hippie van now and all of the
slime's gone
has he cleaned up the sludge
has he
has he cleaned up that environmental
disaster
renbob's hippie van
what is going on here
and he's selling he's selling shoes for
a diamond
sandals of solidarity all right i guess
we're gonna be wearing these but no
that's a bad idea
i guess i'll take a pair of sandals
because he's uh doing a good job of um
keeping it clean look there's even fish
the fish have returned this is so weird
this is so weird i'm just gonna go back
to making my elytra course
now remember when i'm making this
electric course throughout this season
or this series i have got permission
from everyone to make this and attach it
to buildings because everyone is
actually really excited to actually have
a go at playing my elytra course so
no one is upset or anything i've got
permission from absolutely everybody to
make these rings i think people have
been waiting for someone to make one of
these so i'm thinking one here and maybe
i'm gonna make this one a little bit on
the small side
now two by two holes are particularly
difficult to get through
there we go so we got a ring i'll make
that a bit tidier later on but it is
easy it is actually possible to fly
through these without without getting
hurt it's just a little bit on the more
difficult side
it's even possible to get through one
wide holes but i don't know if i'm
actually going to do that i mean you can
get through
these weird shapes here like you could
even go through this one
i think i just made like i think i just
made a roblox sound by accident i didn't
i didn't mean to do that
i'm so weird sometimes
oh and also we should check on our
diorite box or whatever
also we should check on our little
diorite venture
remember last episode we made like a
secret diorite thing
hello
someone has purchased all of the diorite
someone needs a lot of bird poop i don't
even have any more diuretic to stock it
up with i used all of it for that so
we just made a little bit of money easy
peasy i think i'm gonna restock that as
soon as i find more diorite
and as we were doing that stress monster
has come online so hopefully she sticks
around for like five minutes so that we
can do this leaflet campaign on her all
right i need to empty everything and i
mean everything
into this shulker box so i need to grab
all of this paper i even need to i need
to get rid of everything my tools my
armor
everything okay i've got the minimum my
elytra is almost dead and we're going to
do a leaflet drop
for
stress and i've even added a few in here
that are specifically tailored for
stress so this is this is some targeted
marketing right here right so we've got
all the paper it's time to trial
this leaflet drop i just need to go and
find her wherever she is maybe 16
rockets isn't gonna cut it you know how
i fly all right now we just need to go
on the lookout for her so that we can
actually do this leaflet drop now if
this goes well
we could do this for every single hermit
on the server once sahara opens this is
a this is a trial this is a marketing
trial this is a focus group if you like
to see if this sort of thing works now
where is she she might be in the
shopping district i don't see her the
only other logical place she would be is
at her base
but it would work best if she doesn't
have a clue that i'm coming
so if i fly up pretty high
then she may not even see me get there
there she is there she is okay i'm
really high up i'd be surprised if she
hears the rockets
or anything
i can't even see her so if i get a
little bit lower there she is all right
this is going to take some intense
flying
shoba tara
that
is how you drop leaflets on someone
she's not even picking up the leaflets
[Laughter]
oh
no
i'm back at sport island
what is this
well i still haven't sold my did you die
box
well i think it works
whether she actually shops at sahara oh
dear it looks like a few of my cows got
out
these better not be betsy and bertie no
it looks like they were just
escaping cows
do you feel like you want to shop at
sahara maybe well i could get all my
stuff back now
and then i put all of my stuff on and
then we have a leaflet campaign
i really i think i made her jump there
i'm really
i think i made her jump that's the thing
though i when you're doing these leaflet
drops you've got to be accurate you have
to fall just in front of them if you
fall behind them
you won't get the effect so i guess now
i need to i need to do this i need to
put a chest right here elytra return
thank you
now one thing that i actually do need to
do is is this
i need to not block it off because we're
obviously still working in here
but i need to add a sign saying coming
soon to a shopping district near you
because sahara still has a long way to
go and with mumbo moving house and stuff
it's just me and iskall and there's a
lot of like redstone stuff to do but as
you can see sahara is well on its way
the infinity room is now complete along
with a little prank that i hope to
finish off hopefully next episode i can
organize a meeting with iska mumbo and
we can see that play out in all of its
hilarity i can't believe how much time i
spent making that infinity room and it's
actually smaller than the one i've got
over there
absolutely ridiculous we also made some
progress on the electric course a little
bit
ren is now a hippie and we trialled out
our leaflet campaign but i'm afraid that
is all we have time for today i'm afraid
i wasted quite a lot of time
breeding cows
thank you very much for watching
everyone i hope you enjoyed today's
episode and i'll see you in the next one
good
bye
uh-oh